http://www.oldworldchristmas.com/pages/privacy-policy

You are using an unsupported version of Internet Explorer. Please update your browser to the latest version, or download Chrome or Firefox.
Last day to order with standard shipping is 12/7 to receive by Christmas. Expedited shipping is available through noon (PST) on 12/23. Hurry and order now!
Cart
(0)
Search
Submit an Ornament Idea!
Wholesale Login
Login
|
Cart
Checkout (0 | $0.00 USD)
Search
New
Mid-Year
New
Ornaments
View All
Animals & Pets
Birds
K-9 Cottages
Ginger Boo!
Ginger Cottages Displays
Coca-Cola
Accessories & Decor
View All
Snow Globes
Hooks & Stands
Night Lights
Tree Tops
Collection Replacement
Web Specials
Wishlist
Log In
Wholesale Log In
Cart (0)
Wholesale Application
×
Want to learn more about becoming a wholesale customer? Visit our wholesale christmas ornaments page. If you're ready to fill out an application, you can do so below!
Your browser does not support iframes.
Privacy Policy
Share
Facebook
Twitter
GooglePlus
Email
Privacy Policy
Keeping your personal information secure and ensuring your understanding of how we use that information is important to us at Old World Christmas. Our goal is to help you understand how the personal information you choose to share with us through the Old World Christmas web site is collected, used and maintained.
Guests and Registered Users
You can visit this site to read about our company, its products and services, or other features, all without giving us any personal information about yourself. We may collect anonymous, aggregate information about how our site is accessed by you, such as IP address, referring site, domain name, time spent at the site or web pages visited.
Categories of Information Collected
Registration Information: Some of the features on the site require registration before you can use them. If you register to use the site, you choose to provide us with certain personal information such as your name, address, e-mail address and telephone number. You can update registration information online. You may change your password at any time.Service and Transaction Information: When you use a password or a similar identifier to access the site, we will recognize your identifier and may collect various categories of information about you such as information you give us, data related to your use of the site and its services and information about your transactions, interactions, and communications with us.
Use of Collected Information
We do not sell or market your personal information or personalized data to other organizations. The personal information you provide and the personalized data you create and save on the site is used to provide better service to you and to inform you of products, services, or other opportunities that may be available. This may include disclosure of such information to employees, representatives, officers, agents, affiliates, government and regulatory entities, third parties, and service providers. Such information and data will also be used to administer our business, the site, and our services in a manner consistent with this privacy statement. If you provide us with your name, address, telephone number or e-mail address, or have done so in the past, Old World Christmas may contact you by telephone, mail or e-mail.
Aggregate Information
If you anonymously visit or browse the site without registering or logging on with a username, password or other registration code, we do not collect your personal information unless you disclose it to us (e.g., e-mail address). We may collect aggregate, technical information that tracks site use including browser type, IP address, domain name, number or type of pages visited and time spent on the site. We may use such information in a variety of ways including analyzing trends, visitor interests, or to improve the site.
Other Sites and Services
This site may contain links to other Internet sites not under our direction or control. This privacy statement does not apply to those sites. We are not responsible for such sites, cannot control how such sites use personal information, cookies or other data, and their representations do not apply to this site. You should always review the privacy representations of those sites that you link to before you use them and particularly before you share personal information.
Security
Old World Christmas maintains your personal information and data according to strict standards of security and confidentiality. Online access to your information is only possible through a secure (SSL capable) web browser. SSL capable web browsers support encryption technology, which helps prevent unauthorized users from viewing your account information as it travels over the Internet.
Free shipping on orders over $50 in the US!
Have a story about your favorite ornament?Share it with us now!
Submit an Ornament Idea!
Stay up to date with the news and announcements from Old World Christmas!
Right
Privacy Policy |
Copyright © 2019. All rights reserved.
